Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXXIX is arranged in 576 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXXIX. RULES
  - Sub-Series 279-0. Rules
    - General. Military Service, 1940-1944 (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - Vacations. Veterans. Credit for Army Service, 1946-1949 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - General. Correspondence with General Chairmen Concerning Sunday and Holiday Work Rule, 1946 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - General. Correspondence Used in Connection with Representation Cases. Western Pacific-Texas and Pacific, Chicago and Northwestern Railway, 1946 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - General. Typical Rules. Outside Industry Agreements, 1940-1945 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - General. Survey With Respect to Rules and Practices Covering Vacations, Sick Leave, and Saturday Afternoons Off on the Western Railroads, 1933-1934 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - General. Survey With Respect to Rules and Practices Covering Vacations, Sick Leave, and Saturday Afternoons Off on the Western Railroads, 1933-1934 (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - General. Canada, 1954 (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Canadian Health and Welfare Movement, 1958 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Canadian Health and Welfare Movement, 1955-1957 (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - NMB Case No. A-4850, Interpretation No. 38, Paragraph 5(d). L&N, NC&STL, A&WP, Clinchfield, et. al., 1955-1956 (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Rules Changes Movement. Enlargement of Policyholder, 1955-1957 (Box 264, Folder 10)
      1955-September 12, 1957.
    - General. Health and Welfare Policy No. 23111, Retired and Furloughed, 1963-1965 (Box 265, Folder 12)
      July 1963-July 1965.
    - General. Health and Welfare Policy No. 23111, Retired and Furloughed, 1961-1963 (Box 265, Folder 13)
      May 1961-June 1963.
    - General. Health and Welfare Policy No. 23111, Retired and Furloughed, 1957-1961 (Box 265, Folder 14)
      October 1957-April 1961.
    - General. Canada, 1949-1950 (Box 266, Folder 1)
      May 28, 1949-November 13, 1950.
    - General. Canada, 1950-1951 (Box 266, Folder 2)
      November 14, 1950-January 1951.
    - General. Canada, 1951-1954 (Box 266, Folder 3)
      February 1951-April 1954.
    - General, 1942 (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - General, 1941 (Box 266, Folder 9)
      January 1, 1941-August 8, 1941.
    - General, 1938 (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - General, 1937 (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - General, 1930-1936 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - General, 1923-1939 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - General, 1922 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - General, 1921 (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - General, 1921 (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - General, 1952 (Box 267, Folder 11)
      March-December 1952.
    - General, 1950-1952 (Box 268, Folder 1)
      October 1950-February 1952.
    - General, 1950 (Box 268, Folder 2)
      May-September 1950.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 268, Folder 3)
      October 1949-April 1950.
    - General, 1949 (Box 268, Folder 4)
      April-September 1949.
    - General, 1949 (Box 268, Folder 5)
      January 10, 1949-March 1949.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 268, Folder 6)
      September 1948-January 9, 1949.
    - General, 1948 (Box 268, Folder 7)
      May-August 1948.
    - General, 1948 (Box 268, Folder 8)
      January-April 1948.
    - General, 1947 (Box 268, Folder 9)
      July-December 1947.
    - General, 1947 (Box 268, Folder 10)
      January-June 1947.
    - General, 1946 (Box 268, Folder 11)
      July-December 1946.
    - General, 1946 (Box 268, Folder 12)
      January-June 1946.
    - General, 1945 (Box 269, Folder 1)
      January-September 1945.
    - General, 1945 (Box 269, Folder 2)
      October-December 1945.
    - General. 1958 Rules Movement Assessments, 1958-1960 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Featherbedding. Replies to Circular No. 186, 1959 (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Featherbedding, 1959 (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - General. Current Docket. Moratorium Disputes, 1958-1959 (Box 269, Folder 10)
    - General. 1958 Rules Movement (Box 269, Folder 11)
    - Special File. List Showing Carriers in US Where Separate Notices Should Be Served For Wage and Rules Changes. Replies to Questionnaire Requesting this Information, 1956 (Box 269, Folder 12)
    - General. June 1960-December 1962 (Box 269, Folder 13)
    - General, 1958-1960 (Box 270, Folder 3)
      July 1958-May 1960.
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 270, Folder 4)
      March 1957-June 1958.
    - General, 1957 (Box 270, Folder 5)
      June-December 1957.
    - General, 1957 (Box 270, Folder 6)
      January-May 1957.
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 270, Folder 7)
      June 1955-December 1956.
    - General, 1954-1955 (Box 270, Folder 8)
      June 1954-May 1955.
    - General, 1953-1954 (Box 270, Folder 9)
      August 1953-May 1954.
    - Replies to Circular No. 3-60, Featherbedding, 1960 (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - General, 1953 (Box 271, Folder 9)
      January-July 1953.
    - General. Rule "Q", 1955-1958 (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - General. Union Shop, 1956 (Box 271, Folder 11)
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 271, Folder 12)
    - General. Replies to Circular 15-64 dated February 7, 1964 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-0 (a). Rules
    - General, 1943-1944 (Box 266, Folder 4)
      December 1943-December 1944.
    - 279-0 (a7). General, 1943 (Box 266, Folder 5)
      July-November 1943.
    - 279-0 (a6). General, 1943 (Box 266, Folder 6)
      January-June 1943.
    - 279-0 (a4). General, 1941 (Box 266, Folder 8)
      August 9, 1941-December 31, 1941.
    - 279-0 (a2). General, 1940 (Box 266, Folder 10)
    - 279-0 (a1). General, 1939 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-0 (c). Rules
    - General. Military Service, 1944-1945 (Box 267, Folder 9)
      October 4, 1944-January 1945.
    - General. Military Service, 1940-1944 (Box 267, Folder 10)
      1940-September 21, 1944.
    - General. Military Service, 1945 (Box 269, Folder 3)
      February-July 1945.
    - General. Military Service, 1946 (Box 269, Folder 5)
      January-May 1946.
    - General. Military Service, 1945 (Box 269, Folder 6)
      August-December 1945.
    - General. Military Service, 1946 (Box 271, Folder 1)
      June 1946-September 21, 1946.
    - General. Military Service, 1946-1947 (Box 271, Folder 2)
      November 1946-July 1947.
    - General. Military Service, 1946 (Box 271, Folder 3)
      September 22, 1946-October 1946.
    - General. Military Service, 1948-1949 (Box 271, Folder 4)
      August 1948-October 1949.
    - General. Military Service, 1947-1948 (Box 271, Folder 5)
      August 1947-July 1948.
    - General. Military Service, 1950-1955 (Box 271, Folder 6)
      December 1950-55.
    - General. Military Service, 1949-1950 (Box 271, Folder 7)
      November 1949-November 1950.
  - Sub-Series 279-0 (e). Rules
    - General. Disputes Arising Out of the Interpretation of Article VI of the Agreement of November 1, 1956, 1958-1961 (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-0 (Sections). Rules
    - 279-0 (Section 14). Health and Welfare. General, 1965 (Box 264, Folder 11)
      September 8, 1965-December 31, 1965.
    - 279-0 (Section 13). Health and Welfare. General, 1965 (Box 264, Folder 12)
      April 28, 1965-September 8, 1965.
    - 279-0 (Section 12). Health and Welfare. General, 1965 (Box 264, Folder 13)
      February 1, 1965-April 27, 1965.
    - 279-0 (Section 11). Health and Welfare. General, 1964-1965 (Box 265, Folder 1)
      1964-January 1965.
    - 279-0 (Section 10). Health and Welfare. General, 1963 (Box 265, Folder 2)
      April-December 1963.
    - 279-0 (Section 9). Health and Welfare. General, 1962-1963 (Box 265, Folder 3)
      June 1962-March 1963.
    - 279-0 (Section 8). Health and Welfare. General, 1961-1962 (Box 265, Folder 4)
      October 1961-May 1962.
    - 279-0 (Section 7). Health and Welfare. General, 1961 (Box 265, Folder 5)
      March 1961-September 1961.
    - 279-0 (Section 6). Health and Welfare. General, 1961 (Box 265, Folder 6)
      1961 February
    - 279-0 (Section 5). Health and Welfare. General, 1959-1960 (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - 279-0 (Section 4). Health and Welfare. General, 1958 (Box 265, Folder 8)
      September-December 1958.
    - 279-0 (Section 3). Health and Welfare. General, 1957-1958 (Box 265, Folder 9)
      June 1957-August 1958.
    - 279-0 (Section 2). Health and Welfare. General, 1957 (Box 265, Folder 10)
      March-May 1957.
    - 279-0 (Section 2). General. 1958 Rules Movement, 1959 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - 279-0 (Section 1). Health and Welfare. General, 1955-1957 (Box 265, Folder 11)
      1955-February 1957.
    - 279-0 (Section 1). General. XYZ Agreement, 1953-1958 (Box 270, Folder 2)
      1953-November 8, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 279-0-Mil. Rules
    - Military Service. Andrew, F.W.-Bryson, R.L. (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Military Service. Buckingham, H.M.-Channell, O.P. (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Military Service. Clegg, B.H.-Creekmore, T.L. (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Military Service. Darling, J.E.-Doohan, M.J. (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Military Service. Dwyer, P.A.-Fisk, P.H. (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Military Service. Fogwill, R.W.-Hall, R. (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Military Service. Hardy, J.J.-Hyder, C.F. (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Military Service. Jacobs, L.-Kief, C.E. (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Military Service. Kuchard, C.-Loehr, S.V.W. (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - Military Service. Love, H.F.-Mead, H.F. (Box 263, Folder 10)
    - Military Service. Moberly, J.H.-Murray, G. (Box 263, Folder 11)
    - Military Service. Mutzbauer, W.C.-Parker, H.E. (Box 263, Folder 12)
    - Military Service. Pateman, J.L.-Robinson, C.E. (Box 263, Folder 13)
    - Military Service. Rogers, J.D.-Shaw, K.D. (Box 263, Folder 14)
    - Military Service. Simmonds, C.-Stamour, C.E. (Box 263, Folder 15)
    - Military Service. Swan, J.-Wilson, E.J. (Box 263, Folder 16)
    - Military Service. Wilson, W.J.-Wooten, L.L. (Box 263, Folder 17)
    - Military Service. Wright, F.H.-Younger, K.G. (Box 263, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-1. Rules. Atlantic Coast Line Railroad
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1956-1958 (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1951-1954 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1952-1955 (Box 272, Folder 4)
      June 1952-55.
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1948-1952 (Box 272, Folder 5)
      1948-May 1952.
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1941-1947 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1930-1939 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1928-1929 (Box 272, Folder 8)
      May 10, 1928-November 19, 1929.
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1922-1925 (Box 272, Folder 9)
      January 24, 1922-September 25, 1925.
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1921 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - Health and Welfare Joint Movement (Notice Served February 10, 1960), 1960-1961 (Box 272, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - General, 1959-1962 (Box 272, Folder 15)
    - Blackwood Case, 1957-1958 (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Blackwood Case, 1957 (Box 273, Folder 7)
    - Mediation Request, Uniform Pay Day, 1952-1954 (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1953-1955 (Box 273, Folder 10)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1942-1945 (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1947 (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - Case A-692. Exhibits, 1945 (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - Case A-692. Extra Exhibits, 1945 (Box 274, Folder 9)
    - Case A-1600, 1943-1945 (Box 274, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-1 (b). Rules
    - Case A-598, 1939 (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-1 (c). Rules
    - Panel Board Hearing, 1945 (Box 273, Folder 1)
      April 3-11, 1945.
    - Panel Board Hearing, 1945 (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Refusal to Bargain, 1948-1955 (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Refusal to Bargain, 1948-1953 (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1948-1958 (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1951-1953 (Box 273, Folder 11)
      September 1951-53.
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1948-1951 (Box 273, Folder 12)
      1948-August 1951.
    - Scope Rule Work Sheets, A-2836, 1948 (Box 273, Folder 13)
    - Copies of Agreements Proposed by Atlantic Coast Line Management, 1951 (Box 273, Folder 14)
      1951 July 16
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1946-1948 (Box 273, Folder 15)
    - Schedule Revision, 1939-1945 (Box 273, Folder 16)
      1939-April 23, 1945.
    - List of Eligible Voters. Case No. R.1808 (Box 273, Folder 17-18)
    - Schedule Revision, 1945-1947 (Box 274, Folder 10)
      April 24, 1945-47.
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1947 (Box 274, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-1 (d). Rules
    - Case A-1600, 1944-1945 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-1 (Sections). Rules
    - 279-1 (Section 1). Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - 279-1 (Section 2). Union Shop, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 3)
      1956-March 1957.
  - Sub-Series 279-2. Rules. Illinois Central Railroad
    - General, 1956-1959 (Box 274, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 274, Folder 14)
    - January 7, 1954-December 1955 (Box 274, Folder 15)
    - Union Shop, 1956-1961 (Box 274, Folder 16)
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 274, Folder 17)
    - Mediation Case A-6391. 1960-1961 (Box 274, Folder 18)
    - Cases A-1312 and A-1387, 1942-1964 (Box 274, Folder 19)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 20)
      1951-April 1953.
    - Union Shop, 1953-1955 (Box 274, Folder 21)
      May 1953-December 1955.
    - Illinois Central Railroad Hospital Department. Union Shop, 1955-1956 (Box 274, Folder 22)
    - Mediation Case A-5501. 1957 (Box 274, Folder 23)
    - Mediation Case A-4522, 1954 (Box 274, Folder 24)
    - Scope Rule, 1938-1953 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Arbitration Case A-3911. Carrier's Argument, 1948 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Arbitration Case A-3911. Employees' Exhibits, 1948 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Arbitration Case A-3911. Carrier's Exhibits Nos. 2-44;47, 1948 (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Arbitration Case A-3911. Arbitration Proceedings, 1948 (Box 275, Folder 6-8)
      August 3-12, 1948.
    - Arbitration Case A-3911. Statement of Oscar L. Grismore, General Traffic Manager, Sales and Service, 1948 (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - Arbitration Case A-3911. Carrier's Exhibit No. 1, 1948 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - Arbitration Case A-3911. Carrier's Exhibit No. 45, 1948 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Arbitration Case A-3911. Carrier's Exhibit No. 46, 1948 (Box 275, Folder 12)
    - Illinois Central Railroad Hospital Department, 1948-1955 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1957 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1950-1953 (Box 276, Folder 5)
      November 3, 1950-October 29, 1953.
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1948-1950 (Box 276, Folder 6)
      April 1948-November 2, 1950.
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1946-1948 (Box 276, Folder 7)
      1946-March 1948.
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1942-1945 (Box 276, Folder 8)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1930-1941 (Box 276, Folder 9)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1921-1929 (Box 276, Folder 10)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1921 (Box 276, Folder 11-16)
      June-July 1921.
  - Sub-Series 279-2 (b). Rules
    - Case A-1735, 1930-1948 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-2 (Sections). Rules
    - 279-2 (Section 1). 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 275, Folder 1)
      1948-August 1, 1949.
    - 279-2 (Section 2). 40-Hour Week, 1949-1954 (Box 274, Folder 25)
      August 2, 1949-54.
  - Sub-Series 279-3. Rules. Lehigh Valley Railroad
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 276, Folder 17)
    - General, 1956-1962 (Box 276, Folder 18)
    - Mediation Case A-5865, 1958-1959 (Box 276, Folder 19)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 276, Folder 20)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1951 (Box 276, Folder 21)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1947-1955 (Box 276, Folder 22)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1938-1941 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Rules Revision, 1951-1955 (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1937 (Box 277, Folder 10)
      1937 June
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1921-1923 (Box 277, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-3 (a). Rules. Lehigh Valley Railroad
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1947 (Box 277, Folder 6)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1940-1946 (Box 277, Folder 7)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1942-1946 (Box 277, Folder 8)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1942-1943 (Box 277, Folder 9)
    - 279-3 (a1). C-906, 1934-1937 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-4. Rules. Delaware and Hudson Railroad
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 277, Folder 12)
    - Delaware and Hudson Railroad, 1942-1955 (Box 277, Folder 13)
    - Rules Revision -1952-1957 (Box 277, Folder 14)
    - Delaware and Hudson Railroad, 1939-1941 (Box 277, Folder 15)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 277, Folder 16)
    - Vacations, 1942-1946 (Box 277, Folder 17)
    - Delaware and Hudson Railroad, 1920-1921 (Box 277, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-5. Rules. Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad, 1943-1956 (Box 277, Folder 19)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1960 (Box 277, Folder 20)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 277, Folder 21)
    - General, 1930-1943 (Box 277, Folder 22)
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad, 1952-1953 (Box 277, Folder 23)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1952 (Box 277, Folder 24)
    - Teletype, 1948-1949 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad, 1945-1947 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Rules Revision, 1944-1955 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Health and Welfare Joint Movement, 1960-1961 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad, 1957-1961 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Representation Dispute, Case R-1077, 1943 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Case A-1835. Exhibits, 1946 (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - Case A-1835. Hearing, 1946 (Box 278, Folder 8)
      1946 December 13
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad, 1921 (Box 278, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-6. Rules. Cincinnati, Indianapolis, and Western Railroad
    - Cincinnati, Indianapolis, and Western Railroad, 1921-1923 (Box 278, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-7. Rules. St. Joseph and Grand Island Railroad
    - St. Joseph and Grand Island Railroad, 1921 (Box 278, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-8. Rules. Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western Railroad
    - Scranton Transfer, 1956-1957 (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western Railroad, 1947-1948 (Box 278, Folder 13)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western Railroad, 1950-1956 (Box 278, Folder 14)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 278, Folder 15)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western Railroad, 1939-1949 (Box 278, Folder 16)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western Railroad, 1950-1956 (Box 278, Folder 17)
    - Agreement, 1949 (Box 278, Folder 18)
      1949 September 1
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 278, Folder 19)
    - Vacations, 1945-1950 (Box 278, Folder 20)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western Railroad, 1933-1938 (Box 278, Folder 21)
    - Case M-199, 1922 (Box 278, Folder 22)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 278, Folder 23)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1956 (Box 279, Folder 1)
      1951-November 20, 1956.
    - 40-Hour Week, 1957-1958 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - General, 1957-1961 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Rule 8 Dispute, 1956-1961 (Box 279, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-9. Rules. Louisiana and Arkansas Railway
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Vacations, 1942-1946 (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Louisiana and Arkansas Railway, 1921 (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - 279-9 (a). Louisiana and Arkansas Railway, 1929-1943 (Box 279, Folder 8)
      1929-October 1943.
    - 279-9 (b). Louisiana and Arkansas Railway. Cases A-413, A-414, A-435, A-436, 1937-1940 (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-10. Rules. Pittsburgh and Shawmut Railroad
    - Pittsburgh and Shawmut Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 279, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-11. Rules. Bangor and Aroostook Railroad
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1960 (Box 279, Folder 11)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 279, Folder 12)
    - General, 1936-1955 (Box 279, Folder 13)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 279, Folder 14)
    - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1940-1945 (Box 279, Folder 15)
    - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1944-1945 (Box 279, Folder 16)
    - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1921 (Box 279, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-12. Rules. Michigan Central Railroad
    - Michigan Central Railroad, 1957-1961 (Box 279, Folder 18)
      1957-March 1961.
    - Detroit Stock Yard Company. 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 279, Folder 19)
    - Rules Revision, 1952-1956 (Box 279, Folder 20)
      February 1952-January 20, 1956.
    - Union Shop, 1951-1960 (Box 279, Folder 21)
      1951-December 31, 1960.
    - 7-Day Warehouse Operation, 1956-1957 (Box 279, Folder 22)
    - Mediation Case, 1957 (Box 279, Folder 23)
    - Agreements, 1922-1956 (Box 279, Folder 24)
    - Michigan Central Railroad, 1950-1956 (Box 279, Folder 25)
    - Rules Revision, 1939-1952 (Box 280, Folder 1)
      1939-January 1952.
    - Detroit Stock Yard Company, 1940-1941 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Michigan Central Railroad, 1940-1949 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Case A-766, 1923-1939 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Canadian Section, 1947-1948 (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Michigan Central Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 280, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-13. Rules. Central of Georgia Railroad
    - Central of Georgia Railroad, 1921-1937 (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - Agreements, 1941-1960 (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - Health and Welfare. GA-23000, 1959-1965 (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1956 (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - General, 1958-1962 (Box 280, Folder 13)
      August 1958-62.
    - Mediation Case A-6177, 1959-1960 (Box 280, Folder 14)
    - Clerks, 1956-1958 (Box 280, Folder 15)
      1956-July 1958.
    - Health and Welfare, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case A-6062, 1959-1960 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Mediation Case A-5619, 1957-1959 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1960 (Box 281, Folder 4-5)
    - Agreements, 1941-1944 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Clerks, 1954-1955 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - 279-13 (a). Central of Georgia Railroad, 1948-1953 (Box 281, Folder 8)
    - Case A-4048, 1950-1952 (Box 281, Folder 9)
    - Rules Revision, 1943-1945 (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - Mediation Case A-5124, 1956 (Box 281, Folder 11)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 281, Folder 13)